look at the data set that we're looking at right now, we're looking at the data set that
ultimately was published in the New England Journal of Medicine. Very clear that you saw
compelling data with the hand opening time. We saw functional endpoints going in the right
direction. And so we saw everything the way we would expect it. And we have the opportunity
here with a fully enrolled, fully powered phase three study that's going to read out
well ahead of the competition. And I think once that happens would make it harder for
accelerated approval to ultimately happen in the field as historical precedents have
shown.
So, you know, I think it's going to be very interesting to see what we can do with a key
first to market medicine with a key, with a compelling profile. It's going to be very
attractive. And then I would also say that, you know, with the avidity acquisition, we
have not only DM1, but we also have the opportunity to be the first medicine, even if we need to
complete the phase three study in FSHD. So it would be first to market DM1, first to
market FSHD. And now we're increasingly excited as well about the opportunity we're seeing
in the pipeline to address this.
So we're excited to see what we can do and what we can do to address more forms of DMD,
as well as apply the technology of antibody oligo, antibody oligonucleotides ties, whether
SIRNAs or ASOs to our own internal pipeline. So taken together, we think that was the
right decision and everything that we've seen since completing the acquisition continues
to confirm that.
Thank you.
Next question.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Graham Parry from Citigroup. Please
go ahead.
Great. Thanks for taking my question.
Thank you.
Great questions. So on remabrutinib in MS, you've now had three trials read out with
an Orbagio control arm, giving a pretty good view on the annualized relapse rate in that
population. So to what extent can you compare that data to your blinded data in the remabrutinib
phase three relapsing MS trials? And to the extent that you can comment, does that give
you any increased confidence in the ability to meet the endpoint? And also could you just
reconfirm that at this stage you're not seeing any drug-induced lesions?
Any drug-induced liver injury or high elevations of ALT in the blinded data? Thank you.
Yeah. Thanks, Graham. So I don't have any comment on the ARR data. I'm not up to speed
on any blinded views that we have or have not taken on the ARR data. But we do track
the blinded safety data quite carefully. And I think all of the data that we've looked
at and that I've also seen indicates that we don't see any contribution if we assume
that the historical rates that we've seen with teraflunamide in the remabrutinib and